<body style="font-family:Arial; line-height:1.2em">
	<h1 style="text-align:center; color:#008888">RealTextBoxSupportsXHTML</h1>
	<p style="text-align:center; font-style: italic">Eric Voreis - June 7, 2002</p>
	<h2>Contents</h2>
	<p><b>1.</b>   Use</p>
	<p><b>2.</b>   Description</p>
	<p><b>	a.</b>   Supported Tags</p>
	<p><b>	b.</b>   Supported Attributes</p>
	<p><b>	c.</b>   Supported Style Properties</p>
	<p><b>3.</b>   Bullets</p>
	<p><b>4.</b>   Colors</p>
	<h2>Use</h2>
	<p>To have the RichTextBoxSupportsXHTML display XHTML formatted text, set its <code><big>Xhtml</big></code> property to the string of XHTML code you wish to display.</p>
	<h2>Description</h2>
	<p>The RichTextBoxSupportsXHTML is meant to add functionality to the RichTextBox by allowing those who wish to display formatted text to write in elegant <em>well-formed</em> XHTML, instead of <font color="Maroon">cumbersome</font> RTF. It is <u>not</u> intended to display entire web pages. That being said, this control only supports a limited number of XHTML tags which pertain to text formatting. Its <code><big>Xhtml</big></code> property will ignore portions of the input string that contain images, graphics, and other complex elements. If you wish to display such items in a text box, you should copy them from a web page and paste them in a normal RichTextBox control. The following is a list of supported tags, attributes, and style properties:</p>
	<h3>Supported Tags</h3>
	<small>
		<ul>
			<p><code>body p</code></p>
			<p><code>br </code>(must be terminated: &lt;br/&gt;)</p>
			<p><code>h1 h2 h3 h4 h5 h6</code></p>
			<p><code>b strong </code>(<b>bold</b>)</p>
			<p><code>i em cite dfn var </code>(<i>italic</i>)</p>
			<p><code>s strike </code>(<s>strikethrough</s>)</p>
			<p><code>u </code>(<u>underline</u>)</p>
			<p><code>tt pre code samp </code>(<code>this font</code>)</p>
			<p><code>big small</code></p>
			<p><code>a </code>(does not make links, but does <a>color and underline</a>)</p>
			<p><code>ul li </code>(limited support only: see <b>Bullets</b> below)</p>
			<p><code>basefont font</code></p>
		</ul>
	</small><br/>
	<p>All other tags will have no effect on the text, however their attributes and descendent elements will be evaluated. Comments will not be evaluated.</p><br/>
	<p>The box also supports the following attributes on certain elements:</p>
	<h3>Supported Attributes</h3>
	<small>
		<ul>
			<p><code><b>body: </b><i>text</i></code></p>
			<p><code><b>p: </b><i>align</i></code></p>
			<p><code><b>font: </b><i>face size color</i></code></p>
			<p><b>all:  </b><code><i>style</i></code></p>
		</ul>
	</small><br/>
	<p>All tags (even those not supported) may contain the <code style="font-style:italic; font-size:bigger">style</code> attribute, used for <b>inline</b> style sheet formatting. This is the <u>only</u> kind of style sheet formatting that is supported! The following properties may be set in the <code style="font-style:italic; font-size:bigger">style</code> attribute:</p>
	<h3>Supported Style Properties</h3>
	<code>
		<ul>
			<p>font-family font-size font-style font-weight</p>
			<p>text-align text-decoration color line-height</p>
		</ul>
	</code>
	<h2>Bullets</h2>
	<p>Unordered lists are partially supported by this control. They cannot be nested. It is highly recommended that each item in the list be enclosed within a <code style="font-size:bigger">p</code> tag. However, the <code style="font-size:bigger">li</code> tag is not necessary for proper bullet formatting. It will simply add extra space between each line.</p>
	<h2>Color</h2>
	<p>In the <code><big>body</big></code> and <code><big>font</big></code> elements, foreground color may be set using either hexidecimal (#<font color="Red">RR</font><font color="Green">GG</font><font color="Blue">BB</font>) or one of 16 predefined, case-sensitive color names.</p><br/>
	<p>In the <code style="font-size:bigger">color</code> property of the <code style="font-style:italic; font-size:bigger">style</code> attribute, foreground color may be set using either hexidecimal (#<font color="Red">RR</font><font color="Green">GG</font><font color="Blue">BB</font>) or the format:</p><br/>
	<p><code>rgb <i><font color="Red">float </font><font color="Green">float </font><font color="Blue">float</font></i></code></p><br/>
	<p>where each <i>float</i> is a value between 0.0 and 1.0, specifying relative strength between the primary colors.</p>
	<p>Background color changes are not supported in the <code><big>Xhtml</big></code> property. You may change the background of the entire box using the BackColor property.</p>
</body>
